<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Spencer</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Spencer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rushing Rudin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/drafts/rushing-rudin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/drafts/rushing-rudin/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On October 17, 2025, I decided to see how long it would take me to read and do all the problems in Rudin&amp;rsquo;s Principles of Mathematical Analysis, as an expirement to see how &amp;ldquo;productive&amp;rdquo; I can actually be. This is how it went.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, I failed the challenge. I didn&amp;rsquo;t even get through 1 chapter. That&amp;rsquo;s atrocious.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wanting, and College</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/drafts/wanting-and-college/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/drafts/wanting-and-college/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have one and only one goal for this quarter: learn how to learn, how to grow, how to change, how to be wrong.
Steps I&amp;rsquo;m going to take to achieve this goal:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;attempt self study, skipping lectures in 111 and 118 iff I can read on my own. Then I can go at my own pace, and I will do all of the problems and any thing that catches my attention as I work through them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;actively try to fail at things. Hopefully this will create quick feedback cycles and I will be able to learn quickly from this. Also is an attempt to get past the wall that I feel I put up whenever somebody is talking one on one to me and explaining something, because I feel like I should be smart enough to just get it so I often hold my comments in when I don&amp;rsquo;t understand, which is bad, and hopefully this will change that.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;make things. This will necessitate failure, and learning on my own terms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;be very concientious of the value of social interactions. Do I actually want them? are they good for my goals? Perhaps try &amp;ldquo;do not talk to anyone until after 6 pm, or after 8 hours of work, or something like that.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;talk to people who are smarter than me. do not be afraid of professers! they will probably like me.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ask for things I think I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t get. This will hopefully get me used to rejection, and teach me that I can ask for a lot more than I thought I could.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;be as blunt as possible. ask about things if you are not certain.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;free&amp;rdquo; time? art? those are important, probably. invest in community (sandscape), invest in art, invest in thought and expiremtnation and understanding.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Beginning</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-beginning/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;!-- I am an island; you probably are as well.\
I have never really used social media, as I was brought up with people always telling me how terrible and harmful it is. This is true, to an extent.  --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why did I make this website?&lt;br&gt;
Because many of the people I really respect and look up to have personal websites.
And as I think about social media, and what I want out of the internet, I realize more and more that consumer-based corperations handling personal media (instagram, facebook, etc.) is not what I desire.
I quite like the personal website formula: a reflection of self and thoughts in a very self-realized and conscientious manner, not adjusted to fit some corporation&amp;rsquo;s idea of how online communication should and shouldn&amp;rsquo;t work.&lt;br&gt;
This is my website.&lt;br&gt;
My space.&lt;br&gt;
I am God here.&lt;br&gt;
Thank you for visiting.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Church</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/church/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/church/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My socks are chalk white.&lt;br&gt;
Mom yells at me, they stand out.&lt;br&gt;
Wear coal black instead.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sand Dollar</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/sand-dollar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/sand-dollar/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You reach down to pick it up&lt;br&gt;
From underneath the waves, but&lt;br&gt;
Then it is obscured in muck&lt;br&gt;
The dust the sand that you yourself have&lt;br&gt;
Stirred into the water, and so&lt;br&gt;
You must wait patiently&lt;br&gt;
Until the path finally clears,&lt;br&gt;
And then and only then&lt;br&gt;
Can you try again&lt;br&gt;
To reach it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/drafts/family/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/drafts/family/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When I first got to college, I felt like I missed my friends more than my family, and that was a very strange feeling.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pages/me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pages/me/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;!-- I&#39;m Spencer Hill, although that doesn&#39;t tell you much. I will introduce myself in a moment, but first we should have a quick discussion about the internet, growth, and identity, or none of what follows will seem reasonable at all.

The internet, in my mind, has three large positives:
1. Long distance connections with other people, so you can meet cool folks and have good conversations with them
2. Easy access to massive amounts of information, so you can learn and grow really fast and consistently
3. [i know i had something here, but i dont remember what :( ]

On the other hand, it also has many downsides, including:
1. Long distance connections with other people, allowing you to build your own echo chambers and radicalize your own beliefs without any real opposition
2. Easy access to massive amounts of information, leading to many instances of false information and confirmation bias
3. [i know i had something here, but i dont remember what :( ]

I want to use this website to maximize the positives and minimize the negatives (reasonable, right?), and that means laying a few ground rules. --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe we are all some strange mix of the stories we tell ourselves and how others write you into their own stories. So here are some stories I tell myself:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
