<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Spencer</title>
    <link>https://monopolis973.github.io/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Spencer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://monopolis973.github.io/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Me</title>
      <link>https://monopolis973.github.io/pages/me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://monopolis973.github.io/pages/me/</guid>
      
      <description>&lt;!-- I&#39;m Spencer Hill, although that doesn&#39;t tell you much. I will introduce myself in a moment, but first we should have a quick discussion about the internet, growth, and identity, or none of what follows will seem reasonable at all.

The internet, in my mind, has three large positives:
1. Long distance connections with other people, so you can meet cool folks and have good conversations with them
2. Easy access to massive amounts of information, so you can learn and grow really fast and consistently
3. [i know i had something here, but i dont remember what :( ]

On the other hand, it also has many downsides, including:
1. Long distance connections with other people, allowing you to build your own echo chambers and radicalize your own beliefs without any real opposition
2. Easy access to massive amounts of information, leading to many instances of false information and confirmation bias
3. [i know i had something here, but i dont remember what :( ]

I want to use this website to maximize the positives and minimize the negatives (reasonable, right?), and that means laying a few ground rules. --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe we are all some strange mix of the stories we tell ourselves and how others write you into their own stories. So here are some stories I tell myself:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
